I
I don't
I don't know
I don't know where
I don't know where my
Fu
Future
Future wi
Future will
Future will take
Future will take me
Future will take me, so
Future will take me, so, please
Stop
Stop ask
Stop asking
On
Only
Only thing
Only thing I
Only thing I know
Only thing I know is
Only thing I know is that
It's
It's go
It's gonna
It's gonna go
It's gonna gonna
It's gonna gonna be
It's gonna gonna be so
Fan
Fantas
Fantastic
Oh
Oh there's
Oh there's a
Oh there's a mi
Oh there's a million
Oh there's a million diff
Oh there's a million different
Oh there's a million different things
That
That can
That can hap
That can happen
That can happen, so
Gi
Gimme
Gimme a
Gimme a br
Gimme a break
Gimme a break, yeah
Just
Just gi
Just gimme
Just gimme a
Gi
Gimme
Gimme a
Gimme a break
Gi
Gimme
Gimme a
Gimme a br
Gimme a break
Gimme a break, yeah
Gi
Gimme
Gimme a
Gimme a break
Could
Could I tra
Could I travel
Could I travel the
Could I travel the world
Meet
Meet the
Meet the pre
Meet the pretti
Meet the prettiest
Meet the prettiest girl
And
And live
And live for
And live fore
And live forever
I
I don't
I don't know
I don't know where
I don't know where my
Fu
Future
Future wi
Future will
Future will take
Future will take me
Future will take me, so
Future will take me, so, please
Stop
Stop as
Stop asking
On
Only
Only thing
Only thing I
Only thing I know
Only thing I know is
Only thing I know is that
It's
It's go
It's gonna
It's gonna go
It's gonna gonna
It's gonna gonna be
Fan
Fantas
Fantastic
There's
There's a
There's a mi
There's a million
There's a million diff
There's a million different
There's a million different things
That
That can
That can hap
That can happen
That can happen, so
Gi
Gimme
Gimme a
Gimme a br
Gimme a break
Gimme a break, yeah
Just
Just gi
Just gimme
Just gimme a
Gi
Gimme
Gimme a
Gimme a break
Gi
Gimme
Gimme a
Gimme a br
Gimme a break
Gimme a break, yeah
Gi
Gimme
Gimme a
Gimme a break